The Anticipating Capsule
The Anticipating Capsule!
Here to drop off a delivery!
Yes!
Please stamp here.
Thank you so much.
Finally, it's arrived.
I've been waiting for this.
Isn't this amazing? With this tool,
I can fix anything in the house.
Is there anything that
you want me to make?
Nothing I can think of right now.
Then, is there anything
that I need to fix?
Unfortunately, there's
nothing to fix either.
However, isn't this
equipment expensive?
It's little bit expensive...
Because this is the home series.
I want to use this soon.
I know!
I'm gonna go check
out the furniture store.
Alright, have a safe trip!
Mom, I have something that I want.
You want something?
You can use your
allowance to purchase it.
It's impossible to buy it
with my allowance.
Then restrain yourself!
If you can get a good score on your
next test, I'll consider buying you a gift.
Being a grown-up would be so nice...
The grown-ups can buy
whatever they want.
They can buy whatever they
want because they have jobs.
You can also become a grown-up.
I can't wait until
I become a grown-up.
I want to buy things now.
I can't do that for you.
I know! The grown-ups works in order
to buy whatever they want, right?
So you're going to find a job?
That's one way...
Can I borrow the items
from the future me?
Borrowing the items from
the future Nobita-kun...
Oh, I know!
I have the gadget for that!
The Anticipating Capsule!
This capsule will allow
you to rent any item...
...from yourself, ten years
from now, for 30 minutes!
That's great! Let's rent it!
What should I do now?
First, put your hand here.
Like this?
Nobita Nobi
You can see yourself in the screen.
Next, you can press the button and
say the item that you want to rent.
But, you're only able to rent
if the future Nobita-kun has it.
Hmm, what should I rent...?
I got it!
I want to borrow the jet plane
that I'll have someday.
I want to rent my jet plane!
The item that you want to rent isn't available in the future.
"The item that you want to rent isn't available in the future."
It means the future Nobita-kun
doesn't have a jet plane.
That's disappointing.
Whatever! The thing that I want
the most right now is an RC car.
I want to rent an RC car!
Whoa! It's a classic RC car!
The future me has good taste!
Remember! You can only
rent it for 30 minutes.
Let's go!
This is so easy to control!
It runs really well!
I-I-I-It disappeared!
That's because it's
been 30 minutes.
What? 30 minutes already?
The latest Goro-Goro Comic about
Super Birdman is so interesting.
Yeah, I can't wait for the next issue.
I wonder what will happen next...
Did you hear that, Nobita-kun?
Yeah!
I want to rent next month's
Goro-Goro Comic!
Whoa! The Anticipating
Capsule is so cool!
Birdman is so cool!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
Finally, it's over...
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
WHAT?!
BIRD-
MAN!
To Be Continued
What are you reading, Nobita?
This magazine.
Oh, it just Goro-Goro...
What? That wasn't this month's issue.
So it's next month's?
What happens next?
What does Super Birdman do?
If you are curious,
you can read it.
Thank you, Nobita!
Faster, faster!
W-W-Wait a minute.
Here's the page, Super Birdman!
Birdman the Superman
Gorogon Club
I-It disappeared!
Let's visit Shizuka-chan's
house, Doraemon!
Minamoto
You're so cool, Wataru-san!
That's true.
You're not just handsome,
you're also hardworking.
No, I've just happened to be lucky.
Wataru-kun, since you were a child,
you've always studied hard.
That's true. I've always
admired you, Wataru-kun.
Speaking of that...
When she was a little girl, Shizuka, would always say that, she wanted to marry Wataru-kun. in the future.
Don't bring that up, Mom.
It's so embarrassing.
Shizuka-chan...
They seem so close to each other...
Doraemon, my future wife
is Shizuka-chan, right?
I'm not too sure.
The future can always change...
Oh, no! It would be troublesome
if the future were to change.
I'm just saying...
I know, we can just use
the capsule to check.
I'll borrow this!
You can't do that, Nobita-kun!
I... I want to rent my future wife!
I must be dreaming now.
I have to return to the party.
Jaiko-chan...
Something might
happen in the future.
Let's have a look at that future.
O-Okay!
Go to the time right before we
rented the Future Jaiko-chan.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please clap your hands!
As I expected, my future
wife really is Jaiko-chan.
N-Nobita-kun?!
Nobita-kun?
Takeshi-san, wake up!
The ceremony has started.
No matter how happy he is,
he drinks too much.
Christine-sensei, in her
wedding dress, is escorted by...
Her brother's best friend,
Nobi Nobita-san.
Please give a round of applause!
Congratulations, Jaiko-chan...
No, I mean Christine-sensei.
Your latest work, Wedding Melon,
is really interesting.
Thank you, Nobita-san!
Don't they look like
a married couple?
Yeah, I think so...
This is not a wedding party,
it's a release ceremony
for her latest work.
He's not even listening to this.
Now, the moment that everyone have been waiting for...
Christina Goda-sensei 's speech!
Alright!
This is the moment when she disappeared
because of the Anticipating Capsule.
Go back to the time right after we
rented the future Jaiko-chan!
Nobita-kun?
Wake up, Nobita-kun!
Finally, you're up.
Where I am?
We're back home.
I remember now! I passed out
at Jaiko-chan's wedding party.
What should I do to fix my future?
The party earlier wasn't
your wedding party.
Oh, really?
Then why was she wearing a wedding dress, if it's not a wedding party?
It's for Jaiko-chan 's new
manga, Wedding Melon,
which has sold over
500 million copies.
She was about to give her speech
when you pressed the rental request.
Oh, I see...
So that means that I still might
get married to Shizuka-chan, right?
I'm not sure about that.
Whatever happens to your future
can still change from what it is now!
You need to stay alert, Nobita-kun.
You never know if Shizuka-chan
will fall in love with someone else.
Ah, speaking of...
Who was the high school guy earlier?
I'm going to check it out!
See you next time, Wataru-san!
See you!
Shizuka-chan!
Oh, Nobita-san!
Who was that high school guy?
Oh, you mean Wataru-san?
He's my uncle's oldest son,
who I've known since I was a kid
Shizuka-chan, I will work hard,
harder than that guy did!
Why?
I'll work hard to try and
pass the test this time,
even though I can't get a perfect
score like you and Dekisugi do.
Isn't that a good thing...?
Because of that, please trust
and keep in touch in me.
I would like to rent
Nobita-kun's next test results.
Whoa, this time Nobita-kun
really worked hard.
I need to rush back to
give the speech now.
Was it because I stayed up all night?
This feels like a dream.
How do I get back to the ceremony?
Why does she look so weird?
What an idea for a mysterious story!
Let's write it now!